Guide to the Washington State Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- WASHINGTON STATE NURSES ASSOCIATION, 1908-1980; RECORD GROUP I
  - DISTRICT CORRESPONDENCE, MINUTES AND NEWSLETTERS, 1921-1975; SERIES III (Box-folder 14/19-15/18, 28/47, 38/1-38/53, 39/10-39/34, 60/18-60/56)
    - Lower Columbia District #10: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/31)
    - Lower Columbia District #10: minutes, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 60/32)
    - Mt. Adams District #28, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 39/34)
    - Mt. Adams District #28: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/42)
    - Mt. Adams District #28: minutes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/43)
    - Mt. Adams District #28: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/22)
    - Mt. Adams District #28: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/23)
    - Mt. Adams District #28, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/33)
    - Mt. Baker District #1, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 39/10)
    - Mt. Baker District #1: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/44)
    - Mt. Baker District #1: minutes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/45)
    - Mt. Baker District #1: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/24)
    - Mt. Baker District #1: minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38/25)
    - Mt. Baker District #1: newsletters, 1971 (Box-folder 38/26)
    - Mt. Baker District #1, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/34)
    - Ocean Beach District #21: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/46)
    - Ocean Beach District #21, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/35)
    - Okanogan County District #20, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/29)
    - Okanogan County District #20: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/47)
    - Okanogan County District #20: minutes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14/48)
    - Okanogan County District #20: correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38/27)
    - Okanogan County District #20, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/36)
    - Olympic Peninsula District #12, 1950-1965 (Box-folder 39/21)
    - Olympic Peninsula District #12: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/49)
    - Olympic Peninsula District #12: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/28)
    - Olympic Peninsula District #12, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/37)
    - Pacific County District #27, 1948-1965 (Box-folder 39/33)
    - Pacific County District #27: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/50)
    - Pacific County District #27, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/38)
    - Pierce County District #3, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/12)
    - Pierce County District #3: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/51)
    - Pierce County District #3: minutes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/52)
    - Pierce County District #3: newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Pierce County District #3: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/29)
    - Pierce County District #3: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/30)
    - Pierce County District #3: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/31)
    - Pierce County District #3: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/39)
    - Pierce County District #3: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/40)
    - Pierce County District #3: newsletters, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/41)
    - Shelton District #22, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/30)
    - Shelton District #22: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Shelton District #22, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/42)
    - Skagit and Island County District #16, 1948-1965 (Box-folder 39/25)
    - Skagit & Island County District #16: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Skagit & Island County District #16: minutes, 1968 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Skagit & Island County District #16: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/32)
    - Skagit & Island County District #16: minutes, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 38/33)
    - Skagit & Island County District #16: newsletters, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 38/34)
    - Skagit and Island County District #16, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/43)
    - Snohomish County District #9, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 39/18)
    - Snohomish County District #9: correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Snohomish County District #9: minutes and newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Snohomish County District #9: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/35)
    - Snohomish County District #9: minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 38/36)
    - Snohomish County District #9: newsletters, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 38/37)
    - Snohomish County District #9: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/44)
    - Snohomish County District #9: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/45)
    - Tri-City Area District #15, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/24)
    - Tri-City Area District #15: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Tri-City Area District #15: minutes and newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Tri-City Area District #15: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/38)
    - Tri-City Area District #15: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/39)
    - Tri-City Area District #15: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/40)
    - Tri-City Area District #15, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/46)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 39/20)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11: minutes and newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/41)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11: minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 38/42)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/43)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/47)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/48)
    - Fort Vancouver District #11: newsletters, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/49)
    - Walla Walla District #5, 1965 (Box-folder 39/14)
    - Walla Walla District #5: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Walla Walla District #5: minutes and newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Walla Walla District #5: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/44)
    - Walla Walla District #5: minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38/45)
    - Walla Walla District #5: newsletters, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 38/46)
    - Walla Walla District #5: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/50)
    - Walla Walla District #5: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/51)
    - Wenatchee District #7, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/16)
    - Wenatchee District #7: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Wenatchee District #7: minutes and newsletters, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Wenatchee District #7: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/47)
    - Wenatchee District #7: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/48)
    - Wenatchee District #7: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/49)
    - Wenatchee District #7, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/52)
    - Whitman County District #14: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Whitman County District #14, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/23)
    - Whitman County District #14: minutes and newsletters, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - Whitman County District #14, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38/50)
    - Whitman County District #14, 1974 (Box-folder 60/53)
    - Yakima Valley District #6, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/15)
    - Yakima Valley District #6: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/17)
    - Yakima Valley District #6: minutes and newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Yakima Valley District #6: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/51)
    - Yakima Valley District #6: minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 38/52)
    - Yakima Valley District #6: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/53)
    - Yakima Valley District #6: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/54)
    - Yakima Valley District #6: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/55)
    - Yakima Valley District #6: newsletters, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/56)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, SERIES IV
    - General Correspondence, 1912-1979; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 1/4-1/13, 15/20-16/21, 29/1-29/42, 39/35-40/18, 49/15-51/14, 61/1-62/19, 71/1-71/2)
      - General correspondence, 1930-1937 (Box-folder 71/1)
      - General correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 71/2)
      - Correspondence, 1949-1958 (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Licensed Practical Nurses' Association, 1951-1960 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Other state nursing associations, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS) (part 1 of 2), 1958-1963 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS) (part 2 of 2), 1958-1963 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Washington State Hospital Association, 1949-1957 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Washington State Board for Vocational Education, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 1 of 3), 1962 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 2 of 3), 1962 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 3 of 3), 1962 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Advisory Council, 1968 (Box-folder 15/19)
      - Aides administering medication in mental hospitals, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 15/20)
      - Allied Health Group, 1966 (Box-folder 15/21)
      - General correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15/22)
      - President's correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 15/23)
      - Community Health Week, 1968 (Box-folder 15/24)
      - Federal legislation: civil rights acts, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 15/25)
      - Federal legislation: crime prevention (nurse assaults), 1967 (Box-folder 15/26)
      - Federal legislation: debt limitation, 1972 (Box-folder 15/27)
      - Federal legislation: economic security improvements for RNs, 1967 (Box-folder 15/28)
      - Federal legislation: immigration and nationality act, 1966 (Box-folder 15/29)
      - Federal legislation: women in armed services, 1967 (Box-folder 15/30)
      - Paul Jackson, attorney, 1967 (Box-folder 15/31)
      - Legal, ethical and professional standards, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 15/32)
      - Legal, ethical and professional standards, 1970 (Box-folder 15/33)
      - Membership correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15/34)
      - Membership correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 15/35)
      - Membership correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 15/36)
      - Membership correspondence: District #2 (part 1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 15/37)
      - Membership correspondence: District #2 (part 2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 15/38)
      - Mental retardation training program for nurses, 1967 (Box-folder 15/39)
      - National Association of Social Workers, 1970 (Box-folder 15/40)
      - Nurse Practice Act amendments HB 515, 1961 (Box-folder 15/41)
      - Nurse Practice Act and licensing, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 15/42)
      - Nurse Practice Act: recommendations from districts and others (part 1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 15/43)
      - Nurse Practice Act: recommendations from districts and others (part 2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 15/44)
      - Nursing education shortages, 1966 (Box-folder 15/45)
      - Nursing Home Association, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 15/46)
      - Social Workers Practice Act HB 417, 1969 (Box-folder 15/47)
      - Treasurer's correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 15/48)
      - Voting machines, 1970 (Box-folder 15/49)
      - Washington State Citizens for Abortion Reform, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15/50)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing (part 1 of 3), 1967-1970 (Box-folder 15/51)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing (part 2 of 3), 1967-1970 (Box-folder 15/52)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing (part 3 of 3), 1967-1970 (Box-folder 15/53)
      - Washington State Department of Health, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 16/1)
      - 1966-1972 (Box-folder 16/2)
      - Washington State Department of Health. Health Manpower Project (part 1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box-folder 16/3)
      - Washington State Department of Health. Health Manpower Project (part 2 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box-folder 16/4)
      - Washington State Department of Health. Hospital Advisory Licensing Council, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 16/5)
      - Washington State Department of Health. Advisory Council on Institutional Nursing Services, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 16/6)
      - Washington State Department of Health. Nursing Division, 1970 (Box-folder 16/7)
      - Washington State Department of Institutions. Hospital-Community Council, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 16/8)
      - Washington State Department of Institutions, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 16/9)
      - Washington State Department of Public Assistance, 1967 (Box-folder 16/10)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 16/11)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1968 (Box-folder 16/12)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1969 (Box-folder 16/13)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1970 (Box-folder 16/14)
      - Washington State legislation: HB 142, collective bargaining (part 1 of 2), 1955-1958 (Box-folder 16/15)
      - Washington State legislation: HB 142, collective bargaining (part 2 of 2), 1955-1958 (Box-folder 16/16)
      - Washington State legislation: HB 210, 1967 (Box-folder 16/17)
      - Washington State legislation: Referendum 16, 1967 (Box-folder 16/18)
      - Washington State legislation: session correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 16/19)
      - Washington State legislation: collective bargaining, 1967 (Box-folder 16/20)
      - Western Interstate Commission on Higher Education, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 16/21)
      - General correspondence, 1937 (Box-folder 29/1)
      - Incoming correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box-folder 29/2)
      - Incoming correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 29/3)
      - General correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder 29/4)
      - General correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 29/5)
      - General correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 29/6)
      - Alcoholics Anonymous, 1962 (Box-folder 29/7)
      - Allied Health Groups, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 29/8)
      - American Physical Therapy Association, 1966 (Box-folder 29/9)
      - Bureau of National Affairs, 1968 (Box-folder 29/10)
      - California Nurses Association, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 29/11)
      - Cascadia Juvenile Reception-Diagnostic Center, 1966 (Box-folder 29/12)
      - Children's Protective Services, 1964 (Box-folder 29/13)
      - District Associations (part 1 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 29/14)
      - District Associations (part 2 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 29/15)
      - District Associations (part 3 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 29/16)
      - District Associations (part 4 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 29/17)
      - District Associations (part 5 of 5), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 29/18)
      - Inland Empire Nurses Association, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 29/19)
      - Warren G. Magnuson, US Senator, 1966 (Box-folder 29/20)
      - Membership question in Spokane District, 1912-1916 (Box-folder 29/21)
      - Minimum Wage Bill, HR 13712, 1966 (Box-folder 29/22)
      - Washington State Nurses Association Advisory Council, 1948-1964 (Box-folder 29/23)
      - Other states' nursing associations, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 29/24)
      - Other states' nursing associations, 1966 (Box-folder 29/25)
      - University Hospital nursing employees, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 29/26)
      - University of Washington School of Nursing, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 29/27)
      - University of Washington School of Nursing, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 29/28)
      - University of Washington School of Nursing Visiting Committee, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 29/29)
      - Washington State Board for Vocational Education, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 29/30)
      - Washington State Department of Labor and Industries, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 29/31)
      - Washington State Department of Labor and Industries: private duty nurses fee, 1968 (Box-folder 29/32)
      - Washington State. Department of Personnel, 1968 (Box-folder 29/33)
      - Washington State. Division of Professional Licensing, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 29/34)
      - Washington State. Governor, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 29/35)
      - Washington State. Governor: recommendations for appointments, 1965 (Box-folder 29/36)
      - Washington State Heart Association, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 29/37)
      - Washington State Hospital Association, 1966 (Box-folder 29/38)
      - Washington State Medical Association, 1966 (Box-folder 29/39)
      - Washington State. Mental Health and Mental Retardation Planning Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 29/40)
      - Washington State Nursing Home Association, 1957-1966 (Box-folder 29/41)
      - Washington State Public Health Association, 1954-1965 (Box-folder 29/42)
      - General correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 39/35)
      - General correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder 39/36)
      - General correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder 39/37)
      - General correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 39/38)
      - Hospital Licensing Advisory Council, 1955-1965 (Box-folder 39/39)
      - International Council of Nurses (part 1 of 2), 1949-1964 (Box-folder 39/40)
      - International Council of Nurses (part 2 of 2), 1949-1964 (Box-folder 39/41)
      - Licensed practical nurses - injections and medications, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 39/42)
      - Licensed practical nurse medication course, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 39/43)
      - Licensed Practical Nurses Association Washington State, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 39/44)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS), 1965 (Box-folder 39/45)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing Registration (part 1 of 2), 1956-1965 (Box-folder 39/46)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing Registration (part 2 of 2), 1956-1965 (Box-folder 39/47)
      - Washington State Board of Practical Nurse Examiners, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 39/48)
      - Washington State. Department of Health, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 39/49)
      - Washington State. Department of Institutions, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/50)
      - Washington State. Department of Licensing, 1954-1965 (Box-folder 39/51)
      - Washington State. Department of Public Assistance, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 39/52)
      - Washington State Joint Commission for the Improvement of the Care of the Patient (part 1 of 2), 1954-1963 (Box-folder 39/53)
      - Washington State Joint Commission for the Improvement of the Care of the Patient (part 2 of 2), 1954-1963 (Box-folder 39/54)
      - Washington State League for Nursing (part 1 of 3), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 40/1)
      - Washington State League for Nursing (part 2 of 3), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 40/2)
      - Washington State League for Nursing (part 3 of 3), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 40/3)
      - Washington State Medical Association (part 1 of 4), 1950-1965 (Box-folder 40/4)
      - Washington State Medical Association (part 2 of 4), 1950-1965 (Box-folder 40/5)
      - Washington State Medical Association (part 3 of 4), 1950-1965 (Box-folder 40/6)
      - Washington State Medical Association (part 4 of 4), 1950-1965 (Box-folder 40/7)
      - Washington State Nursing Home Advisory Council, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 40/8)
      - Washington State Tuberculosis Association, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 40/9)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 1 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 40/10)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 2 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 40/11)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 3 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 40/12)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 1 of 2), 1964 (Box-folder 40/13)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 2 of 2), 1964 (Box-folder 40/14)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 1 of 4), 1965 (Box-folder 40/15)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 2 of 4), 1965 (Box-folder 40/16)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 3 of 4), 1965 (Box-folder 40/17)
      - Memoranda to district nursing associations (part 4 of 4), 1965 (Box-folder 40/18)
      - General correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49/15)
      - General correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49/16)
      - American Management Association, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 49/17)
      - American Public Health Association, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 49/18)
      - American Society of Association Executives, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 49/19)
      - Auditor, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 49/20)
      - Board of directors, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49/21)
      - Board parliamentarian, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49/22)
      - Council on Collegiate Nursing Education, 1971 (Box-folder 49/23)
      - Emergency Department Nurses Association, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49/24)
      - Emergency medical services, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49/25)
      - Governor's Commission on the Status of Women, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 49/26)
      - Insurance claims / requests (part 1 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 49/27)
      - Insurance claims / requests (part 2 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 49/28)
      - International Council of Nurses, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 49/29)
      - Forrest T. Jones & Company, Inc., 1973 (Box-folder 49/30)
      - Licensed Practical Nurse Association Washington State, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 49/31)
      - Loyal Insurance Company disability claims, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49/32)
      - Manpower, Inc., 1972 (Box-folder 49/33)
      - National Commission for the Study of Nursing and Nursing Education, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 49/34)
      - National Education Association, 1973 (Box-folder 49/35)
      - National Health Service Corps, 1973 (Box-folder 49/36)
      - National League for Nursing, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 49/37)
      - National Student Nurses' Association, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 49/38)
      - Northwest Adult Education Association, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 49/39)
      - Pacific Underwriters Corporation, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 49/40)
      - Pacific Underwriters Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 49/41)
      - President's correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49/42)
      - Puget Sound Comprehensive Health Planning Board, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 49/43)
      - School Nurses of Washington State, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 49/44)
      - Sentry Auto Insurance, 1972 (Box-folder 49/45)
      - Service Employees Union Local 6, 1973 (Box-folder 49/46)
      - State nursing associations, 1971 (Box-folder 50/1)
      - State nursing associations, 1972 (Box-folder 50/2)
      - State nursing associations, 1973 (Box-folder 50/3)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS) -- part 1 of 2, 1971 (Box-folder 50/4)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS) -- part 2 of 2, 1971 (Box-folder 50/5)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 50/6)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 50/7)
      - University of Washington, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 50/8)
      - University of Washington. School of Nursing Visiting Committee, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/9)
      - University of Washington training re environmental controls, 1971 (Box-folder 50/10)
      - U. S. Department of Defense. Army Nurse Corps, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 50/11)
      - U. S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1971 (Box-folder 50/12)
      - U. S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 50/13)
      - U. S. Department of Labor, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 50/14)
      - Washington/Alaska Regional Medical Program, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 50/15)
      - Washington/Alaska Regional Medical Program - Darrington clinic, 1972 (Box-folder 50/16)
      - Washington/Alaska Regional Medical Program - Patient Care Assessment Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 50/17)
      - Washington/Alaska Regional Medical Program - Key Peninsula Health Clinic, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 50/18)
      - Washington/Alaska Regional Medical Program - Vashon-Maury Health Services Center, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 50/19)
      - Washington Secretary of State. Public Disclosure Division, 1973 (Box-folder 50/20)
      - Washington State Blue Cross, 1973 (Box-folder 50/21)
      - Washington State Board of Health, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 50/22)